import { Game } from "../model/game";
export const BasketballGame: Game = {
    round1: [
        {
            title: "Dumb stuff Jon says",
            questions: [
                {
                    value: 100,
                    question: "Uttered after Brink twists his ankle",
                    answer: "Hey man, you ok?"
                },
                {
                    value: 200,
                    question: "Said to justify taking social dance class",
                    answer: "It just fit into my schedule"
                },
                {
                    value: 300,
                    question: "What did we announce in front of a green screen, pretending to be on the table of Meet the Parents",
                    answer: "Milk and Cookies"
                },
                {
                    value: 400,
                    question: "The name of hurricane on the announcements when jon ran naked into the apartment and bit it",
                    answer: "Hurricane Tiger Geiger"
                },
                {
                    value: 500,
                    question: "Phrase yelled from underneath Jon's bed in a successful attempt to scare the crap out of him",
                    answer: "Candy Bars!"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            title: "League Leaders",
            questions: [
                {
                    value: 100,
                    question: "Most wins in a season",
                    answer: "Golden state (with 73)"
                },
                {
                    value: 200,
                    question: "All Time Leader in NBA Assists",
                    answer: "John Stockton"
                },
                {
                    value: 300,
                    question: "Who of the following has NOT led the NBA in scoring for 3 straight seasons: Wilt Chamberlain, Allen Iverson, Michael Jordan, Kevin Durant",
                    answer: "Allen Iverson"
                },
                {
                    value: 400,
                    question: "This player has led the NBA in rebounds 3 out of the last 4 years",
                    answer: "Andre Drummond"
                },
                {
                    value: 500,
                    question: "Lebron James is the only active player in the top 10 of 6 major statistical categories; name 3",
                    answer: "Turnovers, Field Goals Made, Field Goals Attempted, Minutes, Points, Free Throws Made (Dwight Howard also in FT attempted) (chris paul in assists)"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            title: "Where have they been?",
            questions: [
                {
                    value: 100,
                    question: "Roy Williams",
                    answer: "UNC, Kansas"
                },
                {
                    value: 200,
                    question: "Dwyane Wade",
                    answer: "Miami Heat, Chicago Bulls, Cleveland Cavs"
                },
                {
                    value: 300,
                    question: "Kyrie Irving",
                    answer: "Cleveland Cavs, Boston Celtics, New Jersey Nets"
                },
                {
                    value: 400,
                    question: "Steve Nash",
                    answer: "Phoenix Suns, Dallas Mavericks, Los Angeles Lakers"
                },
                {
                    value: 500,
                    question: "Grant Hill",
                    answer: "Detroit Pistons, Orlando Magic, Phoenix Suns, Los Angeles Clippers"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            title: "March Madness",
            questions: [
                {
                    value: 100,
                    question: "This city has hosted the First Four every year since its inception in 2011",
                    answer: "Dayton"
                },
                {
                    value: 200,
                    question: "In 1976, this was the last team to finish the season undefeated",
                    answer: "Indiana Hoosiers"
                },
                {
                    value: 300,
                    question: "Most NCAA Championships",
                    answer: "UCLA"
                },
                {
                    value: 400,
                    question: "This team was the first 16 seed to beat a 1 seed",
                    answer: "UMBC (vs virginia)"
                },
                {
                    value: 500,
                    question: "How many teams in the first NCAA tournament",
                    answer: "8"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            title: "Feeling Presidential",
            questions: [
                {
                    value: 100,
                    question: "This Hall of Fame Laker led the league in assists 4 times",
                    answer: "Magic Johnson"
                },
                {
                    value: 200,
                    question: "This university produced several NBA players, including Markelle Fultz, Terrance Ross, and Spencer Hawes",
                    answer: "Washington University"
                },
                {
                    value: 300,
                    question: "This coach is known as the father of the triangle offense and the Zen Master",
                    answer: "Phil Jackson"
                },
                {
                    value: 400,
                    question: "Sharing a last name with the 14th president, this player won a championship in Boston in 2008",
                    answer: "Paul Pierce"
                },
                {
                    value: 500,
                    question: "Sharing a name with the 5th president, this lefty center attended Georgetown and has averaged 13 points and 8 rebounds a game over his 9 year career",
                    answer: "Greg Monroe"
                }
            ]
        }
    ],
    round2: [
        {
            title: "111 Nostalgia",
            questions: [
                {
                    value: 200,
                    question: "This object hit someone's 'brand ass new car' in the street, almost prompting a brawl outside 111 that Josh ran away very quickly from",
                    answer: "Frisbee"
                },
                {
                    value: 400,
                    question: "What restaurants cups did Michael Ramsey's house place all over the floor of our apartment, preventing us from leaving our rooms",
                    answer: "McDonald's"
                },
                {
                    value: 600,
                    question: "What object did Brink grab when Josh threw Mark up against a wall in his sleep",
                    answer: "Golf club"
                },
                {
                    value: 800,
                    question: "Brink drilled this person in the face with a racquetball",
                    answer: "Aunna"
                },
                {
                    value: 1000,
                    question: "During Cinco de mayo festivities, what did Josh use to hold up the pinata",
                    answer: "A crutch"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            title: "NCAA Name Game",
            questions: [
                {
                    value: 200,
                    question: "What is the name of Miami University's Redhawk mascot",
                    answer: "Swoop"
                },
                {
                    value: 400,
                    question: "This university is the only division 1 school with a fruit as its mascot",
                    answer: "Syracuse University"
                },
                {
                    value: 600,
                    question: "This state's school of design is located in Providence, and their mascot is 'Scrotie the Nads', a giant walking penis",
                    answer: "Rhode Island"
                },
                {
                    value: 800,
                    question: "In 1997, these two universities sharing the nickname 'Wildcats' played each other for the NCAA Basketball Championship",
                    answer: "Arizona and Kentucky"
                },
                {
                    value: 1000,
                    question: "The University of California - Santa Cruz's mascot is named after this gastropod, one of the slowest on earth, moving at a maximum speed of six inches per minute",
                    answer: "Banana Slug"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            title: "Brotherly Love",
            questions: [
                {
                    value: 200,
                    question: "These Spanish brothers have a combined 9 all star games between them",
                    answer: "Pao and Marc Gasol"
                },
                {
                    value: 400,
                    question: "These two brothers are both in the top 10 of career 3 point percentage",
                    answer: "Seth and Steph Curry"
                },
                {
                    value: 600,
                    // tslint:disable-next-line: max-line-length
                    question: "These 3 Duke players were the first trio of brothers in the NBA since the Barry brothers",
                    answer: "Marshall, Mason, and Miles"
                },
                {
                    value: 800,
                    question: "This brother and sister duo are the only ones to both be in the Basketball Hall of Fame",
                    answer: "Reggie and Cheryl Miller"
                },
                {
                    value: 1000,
                    question: "In 2014, the Phoenix Suns had two different pairs of brothers on their team; name them",
                    answer: "Marcus and Markieff Morris, and Zoran and Goran Dragic"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            title: "I Love the 90s",
            questions: [
                {
                    value: 200,
                    question: "This shot-blocking center was known for his trademark finger-wag",
                    answer: "Dikembe Mutumbo"
                },
                {
                    value: 400,
                    question: "This 7'6\" center had his powers stolen from him in Space Jam",
                    answer: "Shawn Bradley"
                },
                {
                    value: 600,
                    question: "Known as the Round Mound of Rebound, this player was awful at golf",
                    answer: "Charles Barkley"
                },
                {
                    value: 800,
                    question: "The 1997 number 1 overall draft pick had to give up on his olympic dreams of swimming due to his fear of sharks",
                    answer: "Tim Duncan"
                },
                {
                    value: 1000,
                    question: "Michael Jordan retired from basketball and spent 1994 playing with this Double-A minor league team",
                    answer: "Birmingham Barons"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            title: "Because We're Well Rounded",
            questions: [
                {
                    value: 200,
                    question: "In 1939, Germany invaded this country to start World War II",
                    answer: "Poland"
                },
                {
                    value: 400,
                    question: "This 1994 film featuring Tom Hanks won 45 awards and was the top grossing film of the year",
                    answer: "Forrest Gump"
                },
                {
                    value: 600,
                    question: "This Shakespeare play features the opening line 'To Be or Not To Be'",
                    answer: "Hamlet"
                },
                {
                    value: 800,
                    question: "What two countries are separated by the Bering straight",
                    answer: "USA and Russia"
                },
                {
                    value: 1000,
                    question: "What is the sixth element in the periodic table",
                    answer: "Carbon"
                }
            ]
        }
    ],
    finalJeopardy: {
        title : 'UNC vs Duke',
        question: {
            value: 0,
            question: "This year, Duke freshman Wendell Moore scored a buzzer beater as time expired to beat UNC. Who was the last player to hit a game-winning buzzer beater in the Duke/UNC rivalry",
            answer: "Austin Rivers in 2012"
        }
    }
};
